"我相信这些原子
"I like to think those atoms traveled
"为了创造我们 穿越了140亿年的时空
"14 billion years through time and space to create us,
让我们相知相爱 让我们成为一体"
so that we could be together and make each other whole."
哇
Wow.
Penny你的呢?
Penny?
哦 对 嗯... 好吧
Right. Um... okay.
Leonard 你不只是我一生所爱
Leonard, I mean, you're not only the love of my life.
你还是我的挚友 而且...
I mean, you're my best friend, and...
我是你的好朋友
you've got a friend in me.
你遇到的困难
You got troubles.
也是我的困难
I got 'em, too.
我什么事都愿意为你做
There isn't anything I wouldn't do for you.
我们会齐心协力 然后解决问题
We stick together, and we can see it through,
因为... 我是你的好朋友
'cause... you've got a friend in me.
那是玩具总动员的主题曲吗?
Is that the song from Toy Story?
他超爱那部电影
He loves that movie.
的确
I do.
- 哇 这场面太美了  - 对啊
- Aw, that was beautiful.  - Yeah.
我是说 虽然不如咱们的婚礼美
I mean, not like our wedding beautiful.
不 我们赢定了
No, we totally won.
Amy 我不理解 我们到底有没有分手?
Amy, I don't understand, are we broken up or not?
好像你下不了决心一样
It's like you can't make up your mind.
因为你没有给我空间去考虑
It's because you're not giving me any space to think.
那你就给我快点儿想
Well, you should think fast,
因为男人一生都可以产生精子繁衍后代
because men can sire offspring their entire lives,
而你们的那些卵子就过期不候了
but those eggs you're toting around have a sell-by date.
Sheldon 你说出这种话让我不纠结了
You know what, Sheldon, you've made this really easy.
你幼稚 自私 刚才还当面侮辱我
You're immature, you're selfish, you just insulted me to my face.
我不需要再考虑了 我们分手了
I don't need any more time to think. We're broken up.
喂 Amy...
Amy...
有人载我回家吗?
Will someone take me home?